gazettereview.com 2016-05-31

# Website Policies - The Gazette Review

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support@gazettereview.com.

At http://gazettereview.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by http://gazettereview.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, http://gazettereview.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
http://gazettereview.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://gazettereview.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://gazettereview.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://gazettereview.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

http://gazettereview.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://gazettereview.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Amazon Affiliate  Disclaimer**

The Gazette Review participates in the Amazon Associates Program.  This program allows our organization to earn advertising commissions by linking to products and services available on Amazon.com

**Affiliate Commission Disclaimer**

Disclosure of Material Connection: Some of the links on content throughout our website are “affiliate links.” This means if you click on the link and purchase the item, our company will receive an affiliate commission. Regardless, our authors only recommend products or services they personally use or believe will add value to my readers. I am disclosing this in accordance with the Federal Trade Commission’s [16 CFR, Part 255](http://www.access.gpo.gov/nara/cfr/waisidx_03/16cfr255_03.html): “Guides Concerning the Use of Endorsements and Testimonials in Advertising.”

**Reviews & Samples Disclaimer:**

A variety of companies provide products or services to GazetteReview.com for free in the hopes that I would mention it on my blog. Regardless, our authors only recommend products or services they believe are good fits for our readership. This am disclosing this in accordance with the Federal Trade Commission’s [16 CFR, Part 255](http://www.access.gpo.gov/nara/cfr/waisidx_03/16cfr255_03.html): “Guides Concerning the Use of Endorsements and Testimonials in Advertising.”

**Medical Disclaimer**

You should consult with a healthcare professional before starting any diet, exercise, supplementation or medication program. Statements on the Gazette Review about products and health conditions have not been evaluated by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration and are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent disease. If you have a health concern of any kind consult with your health care professional. Information presented by Gazette Review is for educational purposes only and is not meant to substitute for the advice of a doctor or other medical professional. The Gazette Review does not make any medical claims or warranties regarding the use of the products listed on this site. The information presented is general in nature and these remedies may not be for everyone. Like other remedies, supplements and herbs do have side effects. You should consult you doctor before taking any medication.

Statements made on this site are not an endorsement of any specific product, or a recommendation as to how to treat any particular health concern. The Gazette Review shall have no liability as a publisher of information or reseller of any products or vendor services, including, without limitation, any liability for defective products.

The Gazette Review makes no guarantee or warranty of any kind, express or implied, with respect to products, information or services on this website, or the operation of this site.

Read all product labels before use. While we attempt to provide as much information as possible regarding side effects and product contraindications, we may fail to cover all pertinent information..
